<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tuva Travel</string>
    <string name="moyie_mubarek">The primary attraction of Khast Imom square is this library museum, which houses the 7th-century Osman Quran (Uthman Quran), said to be the world’s oldest. This enormous deerskin tome was brought to Samarkand by Timur, then taken to Moscow by the Russians in 1868 before being returned to Tashkent by Lenin in 1924 as an act of goodwill towards Turkestan’s Muslims. It is Tashkent’s most important sight. The museum also contains 30 or 40 rare 14th- to 17th-century books among its collection, including one thumb-sized koran in an amulet case. Photos are not allowed. The library is in the southeast of the square, next to the spartan 1856 Telyashayakh Mosque.</string>
    <string name="chorsu_bazaar">Tashkent’s most famous farmers market, topped by a giant green dome, is a delightful slice of city life spilling into the streets off the Old Town’s southern edge. There are acres of spices arranged in brightly coloured mountains, Volkswagen-sized sacks of grain, entire warehouses dedicated to sweets, and the freshest bread and fruits around. Souvenir hunters will find kurpacha (colourful sitting mattresses), skullcaps, chapan (traditional heavy quilted cloaks), ceramics and knives here.</string>
    <string name="the_state_museum_of_arts_of_uzbekistan">The four floors of this excellent museum walk you through 1500 years of art in Uzbekistan, from 7th-century Buddhist relics from Kuva and the Greek-inspired head of Hercules from Khalchayan near Termiz, to the art of Soviet Uzbekistan. There are even a few 19th-century paintings of second-tier Russian and European artists hanging about. There’s an impressive section on Uzbek applied art – notably some lovely ghanch (plaster carvings) from Bukhara, carved wooden doors from Khiva and the silk-on-cotton embroidered hangings called suzani.</string>
    <string name="ilkhom_theatre">Tashkent’s main cultural highlight is this progressive theatre, whose productions often touch on gay themes and racial subjects, to consternation of the more conservative elements of Uzbek society. Alongside the cutting-edge plays (performed in Russian but often with English subtitles) there are also occasional jazz concerts and art exhibitions in the lobby. The Ilkhom’s director, Mark Weil, who founded the theatre in 1976, was tragically stabbed to death in 2007, allegedly for blaspheming the Prophet Mohammed in his Pushkin-inspired play Imitations of the Koran. Imitations of the Koran remains in the repertoire today.</string>
    <string name="alisher_navoi_opera_and_ballet_theatre">Tashkent\'s main opera and ballet theatre is worth a visit as much for its impressive interior as its fine opera and ballet performances. Verdi and Puccini are standards, or be bold and try a Soviet Uzbek opera by Mukhtar Ashrafi. The ticket office is hidden in one of the exterior pillars.</string>
    <string name="google_maps_API_key">AIzaSyDHkf0s0yXHD5O8ybIcEQPCFXW33Nc3L6E</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Карта</string>
    <string name="title">Мобильный путеводитель</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
